I think most of you
really promised to
do the meditation in the next 30 days.
Today is July 19th, so
every day until August 19th. You don't have to
do it for as long as I did this morning.
I just
tried to create a good recording for you.
During the next 30 days,
if you have time, you can also
listen to the recording.
I always do it this way too,
trying to figure out what he
wants to say next, and then at some point
you won't need the recording anymore.
But every now and then you should meditate with the
recording again to check if you're doing it
correctly. The heart chakra
is a very sensitive place to
meditate on,
and you might also experience a feeling of
heaviness and
tightness in your heart. It's
like when you have a chest congestion, a toothache, your hands tremble, and you have
difficulty breathing deeply.
So if you have these symptoms, there's
a very simple countermeasure: bring
the meditation down to your navel. The
navel is the small hole here, the aba
accra.  It's not in that hole, man. The navel
chakra is an abbreviation, as long as the name
is the place one centimeter in front of the
spine at the level of the nail.
So, even a friend can go to
the Alhambra. You can put your finger in
his nail and his friend
checks the height, and then they can
press into your back and say
that there's a navel chakra there, one
centimeter, about 10 mm in front of the
spine.
That's the navel chakra. So if you
feel tightness in your chest,
or you take a short breath, then you can
sneeze, or... you go down to
the navel chakra,
and then someone asked, but
nothing beats there.
You can also imagine something like a
heartbeat there, which doesn't go too far.
If you go a little further down,
then you'll start having six
dreams. If
you go further down, you'll
have constipation. Really, so if you
have one of those two problems,
then go a little further up.
Really, I mean that he